A Day In The Life Of A Fool (Manha De Carnaval); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Man And A Woman (Un Homme Et Une Femme); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Song Of Old Hawaii; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Sunday Kind Of Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Teenager In Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Ukulele And You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Wonderful Day Like Today; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Ac-cent-tchu-ate The Positive; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Act Naturally; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)