26 Miles; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
59th Street Bridge Song, The (Feelin' Groovy); The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
A - You're Adorable; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Day In The Life Of A Fool (Manha De Carnaval); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Man And A Woman (Un Homme Et Une Femme); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Song Of Old Hawaii; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Sunday Kind Of Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Teenager In Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Ukulele And You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
A Wonderful Day Like Today; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Ac-cent-tchu-ate The Positive; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Act Naturally; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
After You've Gone; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ain't Misbehavin'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ain't No Sunshine; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Aint She Sweet; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ain't We Got Fun?; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Alabamy Bound; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
All I Have To Do Is Dream; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
All My Loving; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
All Night, All Day; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
All Of Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
All The Way; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
All Through The Night; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Allegheny Moon; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Aloha 'Oe; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Alphabet Song; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Always; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Amapola (Pretty Little Poppy); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Amazing Grace; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
America; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
America, The Beautiful; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Anchors Aweigh; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
And I Love Her; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Annie's Song; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Anniversary Song; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Anticipation; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Any Time; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
April Showers; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Are You Havin' Any Fun?; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Are You Lonesome Tonight?; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Around The World; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
As Tears Go By; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
As Time Goes By; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Atlantis; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Auld Lang Syne; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Autumn Leaves; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Avalon; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Away In A Manger; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Baa, Baa, Black Sheep; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Baby Face; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Baby Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Baby, Won't You Please Come Home; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Back In The Saddle Again; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Bad, Bad Leroy Brown; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Bang The Drum All Day; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Battle Hymn Of The Republic, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Bear Went Over The Mountain, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Beautiful Brown Eyes; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Beautiful Dreamer; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
(It's A) Beautiful Morning; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Beer Barrel Polka (Roll Out The Barrel); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Bei Mir Bist Du Schon (Means That You're Grand); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Best Things In Life Are Free, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Between The Devil And The Deep Blue Sea; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Bewitched; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Beyond The Reef; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Big Girls Don't Cry; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Bill Bailey, Won't You Please Come Home; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Black Magic Woman; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Blowin' In The Wind; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Blue Bayou; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Blue Christmas; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Blue Hawaii; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Blue Moon Of Kentucky; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Blue Skies; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Blue Velvet; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Blues My Naughty Sweetie Gave To Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Boogie Woogie Bugle Boy; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Book Of Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Born Free; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Born To Be Wild; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Brahms' Lullaby; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Brand New Key; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Breaking Up Is Hard To Do; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Bring Me Sunshine; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Brown Eyed Girl; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Bubbly; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Buffalo Gals; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Build Me Up, Buttercup; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Bus Stop; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
By The Beautiful Sea; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
By The Light Of The Silvery Moon; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Bye Bye Blackbird; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Bye Bye Blues; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Bye Bye Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Cabaret; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Caissons Go Rolling Along, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Calendar Girl; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
California Dreamin'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
California Girls; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
California, Here I Come; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Call Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Candy; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Candy Man, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Can't Buy Me Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Can't Get Used To Losing You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Can't Help But Smile; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Can't Help Falling In Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Can't Smile Without You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Can't Take My Eyes Off Of You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Cara Mia; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Careless Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Carolina In The Morning; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Carolina Moon; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Catch A Falling Star; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Catch The Wind; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Cecilia; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Chapel Of Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Cherish; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Chicago; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Chinatown, My Chinatown; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Chipmunk Song, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Cindy; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Circle Of Life; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Clementine; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Close To You (They Long To Be); The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Come And Go With Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Come Go With Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Come Monday; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Come Saturday Morning (Saturday Morning); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Consider Yourself; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Could I Have This Dance; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Crazy; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Crocodile Rock; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Crying In The Rain; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Dancing In The Street; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Danny Boy; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Daydream; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Daydream Believer; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Deck The Halls; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
'Deed I Do; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Deep in the Heart of Texas; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Delilah; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Devoted To You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Dinah; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Dixie Land; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Do Lord; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Do You Believe In Magic; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Do You Know The Way To San Jose; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Do You Know What It Means To Miss New Orleans; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Don't Be Cruel; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Don't Fence Me In; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Don't Get Around Much Anymore; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Don't Let The Sun Catch You Crying; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Don't Pass Me By; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Don't Stop; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Don't Think Twice, It's All Right; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Don't Worry Baby; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Don't Worry Be Happy; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Do-Re-Mi; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Down At The Twist And Shout; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Down By The Riverside; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Down In The Boondocks; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Down In The Valley; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Down On The Corner; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Down Under; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Downtown; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Dream; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Dream A Little Dream Of Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Dream Baby (How Long Must I Dream); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Dream Lover; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Dreidel Song, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Drifting And Dreaming (Sweet Paradise); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Drunken Sailor, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Duke Of The Uke; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Easter Parade; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Edelweiss; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Eency Weency Spider; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Eight Days a Week; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Elenore; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Enjoy Yourself; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Erie Canal, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Every Breath You Take; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Everybody Loves Somebody; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Everybody's Talkin' (Echoes); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Everyday; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Everything Is Beautiful; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Ev'ry Time I Feel The Spirit; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Exactly Like You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Falling In Love Again (Can't Help It); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Falling Slowly; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Far Away Places; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Farmer In The Dell, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Feliz Navidad; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ferry Cross The Mersey; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Fever; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Fields Of Gold; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
First Noel, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Five Foot Two, Eyes Of Blue; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Five Hundred Miles; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Fly Me To The Moon (In Other Words); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Folsom Prison Blues; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
For All We Know; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
For He's A Jolly Good Fellow; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
For Me And My Gal; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Forever Young; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Freight Train; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
From A Distance; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
From Me To You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Fun, Fun, Fun; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Funiculi, Funicula; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Garden Song; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Georgia On My Mind; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Getting To Know You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Girl; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Give Me That Old Time Religion; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Give My Regards To Broadway; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Glory Of Love, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Glow-Worm, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Go Down, Moses; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Go Tell It On The Mountain; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Goin' Out Of My Head; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Good Day Sunshine; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Good Morning To You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Good Night; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Good Night Ladies; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Good Riddance (Time Of Your Life); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Goodnight, Irene; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Goodnight, My Someone; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Groovin'; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Groovy Kind Of Love, A; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hallelujah; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hanalei Moon; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Happy Days Are Here Again; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Happy Together; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Happy Trails; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hard Day's Night, A; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hard Times Come Again No More; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hark! The Herald Angels Sing; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hava Nagila; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Have You Ever Seen The Rain?; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hawaii Ponoi; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hawaiian Wedding Song. The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Heart And Soul; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Heatwave (Love Is Like A Heatwave); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hello Dolly; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hello Mary Lou; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hello! Ma Baby; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Help!; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
He's Got The Whole World in His Hands; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hey Jude; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hey, Good Lookin'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hey, Look Me Over; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hey, Soul Sister; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
High Hopes; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Home On The Range; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Homeward Bound; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Honey Pie; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Honeycomb; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Honeysuckle Rose; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Honolulu Baby; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hooked On A Feeling; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hot Diggity (Dog Ziggity Boom); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Hound Dog; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
How Can I Keep From Singing?; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
How Can You Mend A Broken Heart; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
How Sweet It Is; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hukilau Song, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Hush, Little Baby; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Ain't Got Nobody; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Can't Give You Anything But Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Can't Help But Wonder (Where I'm Bound); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Don't Care If The Sun Don't Shine; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Don't Know Why (I Just Do); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Feel Fine; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Got You Babe; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Heard It Through The Grapevine; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Just Called To Say I Love You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Left My Heart In San Francisco; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Love How You Love Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Only Want To Be With You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Saw Her Standing There; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Saw The Light; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Saw The Light; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Think We're Alone Now; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Walk The Line; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Wanna Be Free; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Want To Be Happy; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Want To Hold Your Hand; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I Want You Back; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Whistle A Happy Tune; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Will Survive; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I Wish You Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
If I Had A Hammer; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
If We Only Have Love (Quand On N'a Que L'amour); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
If You Want To Sing Out, Sing Out; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
If You're Happy; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'll Be Seeing You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'll Fly Away; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'll Follow The Sun; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'll Never Fall In Love Again; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'll Never Find Another You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'll See You In My Dreams; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'm A Believer; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'm Always Chasing Rainbows; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'm An Old Cowhand (From The Rio Grande); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'm Beginning To See The Light; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'm Confessin' (That I Love You); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'm Gonna Sit Right Down And Write Myself A Letter; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'm Henry The Eighth, I Am!; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I'm Into Something Good; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'm Looking Over A Four Leaf Clover; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'm Sitting On Top Of The World; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I'm Thinking Tonight Of My Blue Eyes; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Imagine; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
In My Life; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
In My Room; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
In The Good Old Summertime; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
In The Middle Of An Island; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
In The Still Of The Nite (I'll Remember); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
In The Sweet By And By'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Indiana; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Isn't She Lovely; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It Had To Be You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It Never Rains In Southern California; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It Was A Very Good Year; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It's A Good Day; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It's A Sin To Tell A Lie; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It's A Small World; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
It's My Party; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
It's Not Unusual; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It's Now Or Never; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
It's Only A Paper Moon; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
It's Too Late; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I've Been Working On The Railroad; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
I've Got My Love To Keep Me Warm; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
I've Just Seen A Face; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Jackson; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ja-Da; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Jamaica Farewell; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Jambalaya; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Java Jive; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Jingle Bell Rock; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Jingle Bells; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Joshua Fought The Battle Of Jericho; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Joy To The World; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Joyful, Joyful, We Adore Thee; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Kansas City; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Keep On The Sunny Side; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
King of the Road; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Kisses Sweeter Than Wine; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Knock Three Times; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Kumbaya'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
La Vie En Rose (Take Me To Your Heart Again); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Last Train To Clarksville; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Lay Down Sally; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Lazy Day; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Lazy River; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Lazybones; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Lean On Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Leaning On A Lamp Post; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Leap For A Man, Girls, It's Leap Year; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Leaving On A Jet Plane; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Lemon Tree; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Let A Smile Be Your Umbrella; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Let It Be; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Let It Be Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Let It Snow! Let It Snow! Let It Snow!; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Let Me Call You Sweetheart; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Let The Rest Of The World Go By; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Let Your Love Flow; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Let's Get Away From It All; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Let's Get Together; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Letter, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Limehouse Blues; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Loch Lomond; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Long, Long Ago; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Longing To Belong; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Look For The Silver Lining; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Lookin' For Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Lookin' Out My Back Door; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
L-O-V-E; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Love And Marriage; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Love Is In The Air; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Love Is Just Around The Corner; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Love Me Do; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Love Me Tender; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Love Potion Number 9; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Lovely Hula Hands; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Loving You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Lulu's Back In Town; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
MacArthur Park; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Make Your Own Kind Of Music; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Makin' Whoopee; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Mama Tried; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Mame; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Mammas Don't Let Your Babies Grow Up To Be Cowboys; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Maneater; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Marine's Hymn, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Mary Had A Little Lamb; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Massachusetts (The Lights Went Out); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Me and Bobby McGee; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Mele Kalikimaka; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Memories Are Made Of This; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Michael, Row The Boat Ashore; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Mickey Mouse March; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Midnight Special; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Miss the Mississippi And You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Mister Sandman; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Mockin' Bird Hill; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Monday, Monday; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Moon River; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Moon Shadow; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Moondance; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Moonglow; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Moonlight Bay; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
More (Ti Guarderò Nel Cuore); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
More Today Than Yesterday; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
More We Get Together, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Morning Has Broken; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Move It On Over; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Mr. Bojangles; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Mr. Tambourine Man; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Mrs. Brown You've Got A Lovely Daughter; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Music To Watch Girls By; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
My Blue Heaven; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Bonnie; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Cup Runneth Over; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
My Favorite Things; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Funny Valentine; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Girl; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Guy; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Old Kentucky Home; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
My Way; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Never On Sunday; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Night Before, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
No Moon At All; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
No Particular Place To Go; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Nobody Knows The Trouble I've Seen; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Nowhere Man; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
O Come, All Ye Faithful; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Octopus's Garden; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Oh Where, Oh Where Has My Little Dog Gone?; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Oh, Babe, What Would You Say?; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Oh, Susanna; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Oh, What A Beautiful Mornin'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Old Cape Cod; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Old Folks At Home; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Old MacDonald Had A Farm; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
On A Carousel; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
On A Slow Boat To China; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
On Broadway; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
On The Beach At Waikiki; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
On The Good Ship Lollipop; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
On The Road Again; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
On The Sunny Side Of The Street; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
On Top Of Old Smoky; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
One Fine Day; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
One Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Only You (And You Alone); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Our Day Will Come; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Over The River And Through The Woods; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
P.S. I Love You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Paddlin' Madelin' Home; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Peace Like A River; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Peaceful Easy Feeling; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Pearly Shells; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Peggy Sue; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Pennies From Heaven; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
People Got To Be Free; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Please Mr. Postman; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Please Please Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Polly Wolly Doodle; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Pomp And Circumstance; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Prayer Of Thanksgiving; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Princess Poo-Poo-Ly Has Plenty Pa-Pa-Ya; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Proud Mary; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Puff The Magic Dragon; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Que Sera, Sera; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Rainbow Connection, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Raindrops Keep Fallin' On My Head; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ram On; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Ramblin' Man; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Ramblin' Rose; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Rawhide; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Red River Valley; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Red Roses For A Blue Lady; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Red Rubber Ball; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Red Sails In The Sunset; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Release Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Return To Sender; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Rhythm Of The Rain; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Ring Of Fire; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Rock Around the Clock; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Rock-A-My-Soul; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Rockin' Robin; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Rocky Top; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Roll In My Sweet Baby's Arms; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Route 66; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Row, Row, Row Your Boat; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Runaway; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Runnin' Wild; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sakura; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
San Francisco Bay Blues; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Satin Doll; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Save The Last Dance For Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Scarborough Fair/Canticle; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Scotch And Soda; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sealed With A Kiss; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Seattle; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Second Hand Rose; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Secret Agent Man; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Seems Like Old Times; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sentimental Journey; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Shall We Gather At The River; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
She Loves You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
She'll Be Coming 'Round The Mountain; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Shenandoah; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sherry; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Shine On, Harvest Moon; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Show Me The Way To Go Home; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Side By Side; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sidewalks Of New York, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Silent Night; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Simple Gifts; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sing; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Singing The Blues; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sittin' On The Dock Of The Bay; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sixteen Tons; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Skip To My Lou; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sloop John B., The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Slow Poke; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Smiles; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Snowbird; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
So Long It's Been Good To Know Yuh; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Some Folks; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Some Of These Days; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Somethin' Stupid; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Somewhere, My Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Song Of The Islands; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Song Sung Blue; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Soon It's Gonna Rain; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sophisticated Hula; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Southern Nights; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Spanish Eyes; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Spooky; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Spoonful Of Sugar, A; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Stand By Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Star Spangled Banner, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Stayin' Alive; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Stoney End; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Stop! In The Name Of Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Stormy; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Strangers In The Night; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sugar, Sugar; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sukiyaki; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Summer Breeze; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Summer In The City; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Summer Wind; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Summertime; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sunny; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sunny Afternoon; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sunrise, Sunset; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sunshine (Go Away Today); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sunshine Superman; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Surfin' U.S.A.; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Swanee; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Sway (Quien Sera); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sweet Caroline; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sweet Georgia Brown; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sweet Pea; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Sweet Someone; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Swing Low, Sweet Chariot; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Take A Chance On Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Take Me Home, Country Roads; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Take Me Out To The Ballgame; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Tammy; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Taps; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Tea For Two; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Teach Your Children; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Tears On My Pillow; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Tell It Like It Is; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Tell Me Why; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Tennessee Waltz; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
That Hawaiian Melody; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
That'll Be the Day; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
That's Amore; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
That's The Way (I Like It); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The "In" Crowd; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Banana Boat Song; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The End Of The World; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Great Pretender; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Hawaiian Turnaround; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Lady Is A Tramp; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Last Time; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Look Of Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The M.T.A.; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Magic Islands; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Open Road; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Shoop Shoop Song (It's In His Kiss); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Wanderer; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
The Way You Do The Things You Do; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
There Is A Tavern In The Town; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
There'll Be Some Changes Made; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
There's A Kind Of Hush; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
These Boots Are Made For Walkin'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
These Foolish Things (Remind Me Of You); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
They Call The Wind Maria; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
This Is My Song; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
This Land Is Your Land; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
This Little Light Of Mine'; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
This Magic Moment; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
This Old Man; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
This Train; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Those Were The Days; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Three Blind Mice; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Three Little Birds; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Thriller; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Tie Me Kangaroo Down Sport; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Till There Was You; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Time After Time; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Time After Time; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Times They Are A-Changin', The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Tiny Bubbles; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Tip-Toe Thru' The Tulips With Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
To Love Somebody; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
To Sir, With Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
To You, Sweetheart, Aloha; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Tomorrow; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Tonight You Belong To Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Too Young; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Too-Ra-Loo-Ra-Loo-Ral (That's An Irish Melody); The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Toot, Toot, Tootsie!; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Top Of The World; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Traces; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Tracy; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Travelin' Man; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Try To Remember; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Turn! Turn! Turn!; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Twilight Time; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Twinkle, Twinkle Little Star; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ukulele Central; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Ukulele Lady; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Ukuleles Are The Best; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Unchained Melody; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Undecided; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Under The Boardwalk; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Up Around The Bend; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Up On The Roof; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Upside Down; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Wabash Cannonball, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Wade In The Water; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Wake Up Little Susie; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Walk Away Renee; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Walk Right In; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Walkin' My Baby Back Home; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Waltzing Matilda; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Wanderin'; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Water Is Wide, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Waterloo; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Wayfaring Stranger, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
We Are The World; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
We Shall Overcome; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
We Three Kings Of Orient Are; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
We Wish You A Merry Christmas; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Wedding Bell Blues; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
We'll Meet Again; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
What A Diff'rence A Day Made; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
What A Wonderful World; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
What Have They Done To My Song, Ma?; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
What The World Needs Now Is Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
What'll I Do; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
When I Fall In Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
When I'm Sixty-Four; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
When Irish Eyes Are Smiling; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
When the Red, Red, Robin Come Bob, Bob, Bobbin' Along; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
When The Saints Go Marching In; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
When Will I Be Loved; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
When You Wish Upon A Star; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
When You're Smiling; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Where Have All The Flowers Gone?; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Whispering; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
White Rabbit; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
White Sandy Beach; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
White Sport Coat (And A Pink Carnation), A; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Who's Sorry Now; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Why Do Fools Fall In Love?; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Wildwood Flower; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Will The Circle Be Unbroken; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Will You Love Me Tomorrow; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Windy; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
With A Little Help From My Friends; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
With A Little Luck; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Wonderful! Wonderful!; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
World Is Waiting For the Sunrise, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
World Without Love; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Worried Man Blues; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Wouldn't It Be Loverly; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Wouldn't It Be Nice; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Y.M.C.A.; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Yankee Doodle Boy; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Yellow Rose Of Texas, The; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Yellow Submarine; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Yes Sir, That's My Baby; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
You And I; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You Are My Sunshine; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
You Are The Sunshine Of My Life; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You Belong To Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You Can't Hurry Love; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You Didn't Have To Be So Nice; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You Don't Know Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You Got It; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You Made Me Love You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
You Won't See Me; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Young At Heart; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Your Cheatin' Heart; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Your Mama Don't Dance; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Your Mother Should Know; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
Your Song; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You're A Grand Old Flag; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
You're Nobody 'Til Somebody Loves You; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
You're Sixteen (You're Beautiful And You're Mine); The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You've Got A Friend; The Daily Ukulele (Blue)
You've Got A Friend In Me; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
You've Got To Hide Your Love Away; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
Zip-A-Dee-Doo-Dah; The Daily Ukulele (Yellow)
